# Dang Viet Hung

With 13 years of experience in the field of software engineering, I have held various positions ranging from developer, tech lead, and manager, to 5 years of experience as a CTO. I had the honor of being ranked in the top 10 CTOs of the CTO Summit 2021 competition, as voted by vnexpress newspaper. I possess extensive knowledge and experience in web development, data engineering, cloud computing, and devops. My ability to build and develop teams from scratch includes activities such as conducting interviews, providing training, and leading teams.

hung.dang980@gmail.com

0908 793 753

Ho Chi Minh, VN

facebook @dang.v.hung.9

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## TSUDAKOMA Corp.

Developer Oct 2011 - Jun 2014

Develop a NAVI system that helps control all textile machines.

- Work with Japanese team to understand Japan culture
- Find the bug deadlock that already exist in 6 months
- Significant reduce first loading program

## Hayabusa

Team leader Jul 2014 - Mar 2018

Web/mobile system development

- Docopri printer mobile application
- Fahasa online book selling business
- EzeePOS Point of sale application

## **Smartlog**

Technical Leader Apr 2018 - Feb 2020

Become the first integrated platform and ecosystem for logistics operation

- Spearheaded team development, training, and growth
- Successfully designed and implemented a comprehensive Transport Management System (TMS)
- Deployment of an efficient Warehouse Management System (WMS)

# Smartlog (https://gosmartlog.com/gioi-thieu/)

CTO Mar 2020 - Present

Become the first integrated platform and ecosystem for logistics operation

- Pioneered the creation and deployment a transportation marketplace platform system to facilitate coordination between truckers and shippers
- Pioneered the creation and deployment container optimization solutions to enhance coordination between shipping lines and truckers
- Established a data warehouse by integrating data from multiple sources.

# 技術

WEB DEVELOPMENT NodeJS, Dotnet, ReactJS, React native, Angular, Docker, Postgres, Redis, Queue, CyPress

**DATA WAREHOUSE** Kafka, Kafka connector, Prefect, Flink, Big Query, Postgres

**DEVOPS** 

AWS, Kubernetes, Terraform, Jenkins, ArgoCD, Prometheus, ElasticSearch, Grafana, Kibana, Logging/Tracing

MANAGEMENT Engineering Management, Agile Development, Project Management, LeaderShip

#### **EDUCATION**

## Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

Oct 2009 - Oct 2011

Master Software Engineer

**Bach Khoa University** 

Sep 2004 - Apr 2009

**Bachelor Information System** 

#### **AWARDS**

Third Prize at Scientific	Research Contes	st for Excellent Students	Dec 2008

Presented by the Minister of Education and Training

Third prize of VIFOTEC technical invention award Dec 2008

Presented by Vietnam Fund for Supporting Technical Creations (VIFOTEC)

Japan Literacy and IT Test (JL1)

Jan 2016

Japan Literacy and IT Test (JLIT)

Top 10 Vnexpress CTO Summit 2021 Oct 2021

Vnexpress

https://vnexpress.net/10-lanh-dao-cong-nghe-tre-xuat-sac-2021-4394153.html

## **LANGUAGES**

JAPANESE: fluent

**ENGLISH**: fluent